

George Siler Designer

1500 James Street Bellingham, WA 98225

☑ Siler.Georges@gmail.com

**%** 703-585-4531

in @george-siler

# ABOUT ME

UX (user experience) designers measure and optimise applications (usually web based) to improve ease of use (usability), and create the best user experience by exploring many different approaches to solve endusers' problems. ... A similar role is that of a UI (user interface) designer.

#### EDUCATION

### Bachelor of Arts | Design

Western Washington University 2014 - 2017

#### SKILLS

Web Design

Creative Problem

#### EXPERIENCE

# Designer | Faithlife

Feb 2018 - Present

As a Designer at faithlife I am responsible for supporting Faithlife's design, marketing, and eccomerce design needs to ensure the end product meets the consumer's needs. I am able to apply design thinking to problem solving, and will work collaboratively to present work with sound strategic reasoning and strong creative rationale. I work to Create satisfying and compelling experiences on our sites, with a focus on reshaping the customer experience to maximize conversions and better empower our customers to become users.

## Freelance Designer

Jun 2016 - Present

From illustration to web design and branding, doing freelance work has given me the opportunity to invest and grow in myself by taking on contract work that pushes me outside of the confines of my daily work. Through freelance design I am able to continue to hone my craft and help facilitate new endeavors with creative problem solving.

#### REFERENCES

Head of Design | Faithlife

### Micah Ellis

Phone: (207) 542-4053

Email: Micah.Ellis@faithlife.com

Art Director | Faithlife

#### **Bryan Hyntz**

Phone: (360) 318-4989

Email: Bryan.Hyntz@faithlife.com

### INTERESTS

Craft Coffee & Roasting

**Traditional Bookbinding** 

**Gardening & Houseplants** 

UI Design Team Lead | Faithlife

Email: Shiloh.Hubbard@faithlife.com

**Shiloh Hubbard** 

Phone: (206) 412-1419

WoodWorkin